OK, so your turn is to take the disk card and basically strip it down.
Go ahead and use your defined props and define the mits to practice defining that on here.
So, I'll see you on the other side.
So, first thing first, let's go ahead and throw on that setup attribute.
So, we can delete that import for sure, and I can delete this.
And then once again, let's just comment this out for the sake of making things easier.
And then we can const, status color equals computed.
And actually, I need to import that.
Let me use the autocomplete to import that rate.
Then that comes down here, that looks good.
And then the disk right now, it won't, it will be broken, but we know that.
So, that's fine.
And finally, we have const, delete this.
It's just a normal function.
And once again, we know that this is going to break.
So, we'll just comment that out real quick.
And we have that, that done.
All right, so now we complete what we want to do.
So, we have type prop types.
And I'm just going to say that there is a dish.
It will be of type dish.
And therefore, when we define the props, we will pass it in via type casting that we have
prop types.
And then we run it as a function.
Don't forget, this part is important because it needs to run.
And then that takes care of all that because the required property is taking care of,
by the fact that it's a property on there.
And finally, we will define the emits.
And this time, similarly, we'll also pass it in the type casting here.
We'll use the parentheses so that the event, what is the event called, is called
delete dish.
And then what are we expecting as the payload?
We're expecting a dish of type dish.
And finally, what will it return?
It's not going to return anything, so it's void.
So, once we have that, we're not quite done yet because we need to actually refer to
the things.
So, we'll have cons props equals this.
And then we can say props that dish.
Status.
And then down here, we can just delete this line entirely because,
and we, oh wait, I did not define my emit yet.
So, cons emit, there you go.
Once I've assigned that, then we can emit.
Once again, control space is, I believe, how most of us should be able to get to it.
That should be mac or PC.
And then that will give you the autocomplete.
Now, if you, you're like me and you have a bunch.
Don't forget that you always have to hit the up key first to get down to the bottom.
I don't know why, but for now, at least that's how it's ordered online.
So, if you can't find it, it's probably because you need to hit up.
Then, from here, what do we need?
Well, we need a dish.
So, props that dish.
There we go.
And so, we can actually see, even the signature here, right?
And the dish takes type dish.
Done.
And I think that's everything.
Most quickly lines, wait, we don't need this anymore.
Unuse voila.
Magic.